SIDNEY HOWES

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER





35 Chestnut Avenue, Ewell, Epsom, Surrey, KT19 OSY

PROFILE

An ambitious, disciplined and hardworking individual keen to progress within the tech industry. Extensive experience working for a global company, with the ability to react well under pressure in a fast-paced environment - offering creative ideas.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Qualified full stack web developer with code institute
- Diploma in Software development
- Ex swimmer competed at national level
 - County Champion
 - London Champion
 - National Finalist
- Level 1 in sporting excellence within the swimming industry
- Level 3 NVQ in aerospace and aeronautical engineering
- Completed B1 modules in aircraft maintenance

SKILLS

HTML/HTML5 CSS/CSS3 JavascriptJquery Django/Python SQL/NoSQL Wordpress

EXPERIENCE

Code Institute

DEC 2019 - DEC 2020

British Airways Aircraft Engineer

OCT 2018 - OCT 2020

British Airways Aircraft Mechanic

SEP 2015 - OCT 2018

British Airways Aircraft Apprentice

SEP 2012 - SEP 2015

Abercrombie & Fitch

SEP 2010 - SEP 2013

EDUCATION

Code Institue

DEC 2019 - DEC 2020 Diploma in Software Development

Kingston College

JUN 2012 - JAN 2015

Level 3 NVQ Aeronautical and Aerospace Engineering

Glyn Technology School

SEP 2006 - JUL 2012

10 GCSE's ranging between A* - C

OTHER EMPLOYMENT EXPERIENCE

- Buro Happold Civil Engineering
- Millwall football club involved with the development of the academy players
- Physical Education teacher/assistant Hinchley wood primary school